Liz Bilashaka

Quality Assurance Specialist + ISTQB Certified Tester



Dedicated software tester professional and quality assurance specialist with a history of meeting company goals utilizing consistent and organized practices. Skilled in working under pressure and adapting to new situations and challenges to best enhance the organizational brand. Familiar with handling multiple projects in highly competitive environments. Great interpersonal and collaboration skills.

_	4	L	_1
\boldsymbol{n}	nı		\boldsymbol{c}
U		u	

Address

Henderson, AUK 0612

Phone

0210606840

E-mail

lizbilashaka@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/lizbilashaka/

WWW

https://lizb.net/

Technical skills

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

Bootstrap

React

Technical Writing

Testing plans

Bug tracking

Test implementation

Defect monitoring

Work History

2021-11 -

2022-03 -

2022-09

Current

Manual Software Tester (Remote)

GameZovah, Auckland, New Zealand

- Write and optimize test cases to maximize success of functional and non functional software testing with consistent, thorough approaches.
- Assessed software bugs and compiled findings along with suggested resolutions for development team members.
- Carried out tests to identify, report and repair bugs and glitches.
- Supported test review, defect control and configuration management within delivery pipeline.
- Defined and identified test cases for new application development.
- Optimized test cases to maximize success of manual software testing.
- API testing

Customer Service Advisor

Xplor Technologies, Auckland, New Zealand

- Aiding clients and companies with billing enquire
- Assist customers in making payment plans through analyzing their financial circumstances
- Updating customer information in the company database
- Performing administrative tasks as assigned by the Supervisor
- Follow up with customer accounts to ensure overdue accounts are cleared

Manual test case preparation

Postman

Regression Testing
Understanding

Test Planning

Background In Agile Environments 2020-11 -

2021-01

2019-01

Debugging

Cross-Platform Testing

Sound quality management techniques

Project Management

Additional Skills

Excellent communication skills

Strong interpersonal skills

Team player

Fast Learner

Attention to detail

Able to learn and adapt to new technology

Ability to work under pressure

Excellent in working in a multicultural environment

Strong oral and written skills

Referee

- Follow up on correspondence between customers and companies to ensure that both parties are on the same page
- Managed over 50 customer calls per day.

Platform Success Manager (Remote)

Digital Oracles , Manchester, United Kingdom

- Competitor analysis keep the competitor analysis updated, in terms of funding received, team size, products
- Created a line of communication with investor and startups to ensure great customer satisfaction
- Oversaw BETA launch of the platform
- Create an internal weekly dashboard analyzing the speed of growth of startups, success rate of startups, overall feedback, number of perks available, number of resources and tools, revenue coming from revs and tools, revenue coming from investors
- Create an Investor update analyzing the number of deals performed, Assets under management, Industries, and business models (B2B, B2C, SaaS, e-commerce, etc.)
- Analyze lists of accelerators and demo the platform to them
- Deliver content for the online platform

2016-01 - Store & Data Manager

Africana Hair Braiding Studio, Auckland, New Zealand

- Analyze product turnover ratio to formulate pricing policies
- Manage supply chain
- Perform data analysis to track and manage inventory turnover in stores
- Created business strategies to attract new customers and enhance profits
- Provided high-level customer satisfaction through customer interactions
- Analyze market trend and implement appropriate changes

Analyze sales and revenue reports and make forecasts

Education

2022-12 - 2023-01	ISTQB Certified Tester Foundation Level Skillsoft - Online
2022-05 - 2022-10	Front End Developer Skillsoft - Online
2022-02 - 2022-11	BBus (1st Honors): Information Systems AUT - Auckland, AUK
2019-02 -	BBus: Information Systems